I cannot tell you I or thank you enough for what you've done for the gay community so
one things I'm proudest of that because
my whole political careers been based on the idea that
we constantly want to include people and not excluded how do we bring more and more people into
opportunity and success and
%HESITATION
feeling hopeful about their lives and %HESITATION but I will say we were we were driving over here today and I I met this I I said it to my staff I said
%HESITATION as as much as we've done with laws and ending don't ask don't tell etcetera
changing hearts and minds
I I don't think anyways been more influential than you on that I really
you know your courage and your just
really likable and so
so as soon as we are so
yelled
you
being willing to claim who you were Ben suddenly empowers other people and then suddenly it's your brother it's your
uncle it's your
%HESITATION your best friend it's
your coworkers and and and then
%HESITATION attitudes
shift and
the Los followed but it started
%HESITATION with folks like you and well out of that yeah well thank you yeah that's about the school
I'm not really gay I
I was you on TV I don't play one on the audio in word and
I had to stick with it because people responded so I have the answer for
used to come to Hong Kong exactly